Adobe Photoshop is a registered trademark of Adobe Systems, Inc., and I am in no way affiliated with Adobe.
Ok, guys.
On this tutorial, I'm going to show you how to make a drop shadow on your tape to make it look a little more realistic.
So, you want to make sure your "Tape One" layer is selected, as you can see right here.
It's selected.
You want to come down over here to your effects, layer style effects tool, and click.
Now, you can go either straight down to drop shadow, or you can actually hit "Burning options".
I'm just going to hit "Drop shadow".
As you can see, it automatically brought me a drop shadow on my piece of tape.
For some people, they would argue that that looks a little too much.
So, what you can do is actually drop your opacity down to fifty percent and your spread to about sixteen pixels.
Not your spread, I'm sorry. The size to about sixteen pixels and the spread at zero. So, as you can see, my-right here, distance: five; opacity: fifty; spread: zero; size: sixteen.
Now you're going to hit "Ok".
I'm going to go over here up to the top, and you can see my piece of tape.
It's starting to actually look like tape now.
Now, what we're going to do is we're going to move on to the next clip, and I'm going to show you how to actually make little cuts into the tape to make it look even more realistic.